New Delhi Police award viewers place
scam involving of a message been sent
out uses of medium to you tech wise
details of messages been sent out the name
of ICICI Bank addicted to customize
and ICICI Bank account from vice city has been
suspended please update Chowk resident
click in will activate ICICI
Bank account abroad link which instigates you this
message has been sent out during summers
personal number and details in
sleeping and urgency * user to click on this
link Delhi Police arrested on this
link is phishing click but European
ICICI login page to extract login
cadets are suppose Delhi Police
ICICI to this point it is difficult note this
app contains information when warn call
SMS and gets there option so trying to get you to
fill in your login credentials
on this point ICICI login page
slide see demonic and bank account and
see your comment
[music]
that  He is Goa to just message 105 things are of very important
mode personal use
icici bank has not send this
message is registered spelling of bank
live is graphically in kare so language
not from icicibank.com domain
name and no value is jo message va random
number morning tax liability office number
special news send out this sms one with
someone from west bengal and its related
apps chemo to clear and dimple aapke 10
minutes morning delhi puneet has developed with
good morning users about adarsh ​​messages
wish been circulating tears good girls number
tele puri se test ne work after numbers ne more
download any app in the instruction
and who make any token payment to can us this